{
    "subject": "resource/Fatih_Terim",
    "predicate": "property/currentclub",
    "object": "resource/Turkey_national_football_team",
    "human_readable": "Fatih Terim's current club is Turkey national football team.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7796868085861206,
            "question": "Does Fatih Terim manage a club team or a national team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7758419513702393,
            "question": "Name the team that Fatih Terim currently manages."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7644615173339844,
            "question": "Which country's national football team does Fatih Terim manage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.751369297504425,
            "question": "What is Fatih Terim's current role in football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6772437691688538,
            "question": "Who is Fatih Terim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.626749575138092,
            "question": "What is Fatih Terim known for in football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6056684255599976,
            "question": "What team is Fatih Terim currently coaching?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.551672101020813,
            "question": "Where is Fatih Terim from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43237951397895813,
            "question": "Is Fatih Terim a football manager?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27868515253067017,
            "question": "Is Fatih Terim a player or a manager?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fatih Terim's current club is Turkey national football team.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4120_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Fatih Terim a football manager?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4120_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Fatih Terim from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4120_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What team is Fatih Terim currently coaching?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4120_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4120_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4120_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4120_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4120_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4120_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4120_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4120_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4120_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4120_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4120_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe triple states that Fatih Terim's current club is the Turkey national football team. However, according to documents 68 and 94, it is mentioned that Fatih Terim left his role as Turkey's national team coach after a fight with a restaurant owner (document 68), and then he was appointed as the coach of Galatasaray (document 94). This indicates that at some point in time, Fatih Terim was not managing the Turkey national football team."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information about Fatih Terim's current club. In fact, some of the documents mention his past roles and positions, but none state that his current club is the Turkey national football team."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Fatih Terim is currently the manager of Galatasaray S.K., not the Turkey national football team.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several texts state Terim's last stint with the Turkish national team ended in 2017, and he has since managed Galatasaray.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Fatih Terim has not managed the Turkey national football team since 2017, according to statement 5.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Fatih Terim has not been the manager of Turkey national football team since December 2017, as stated in context information that he left his role in 2017 due to non-football related issues.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}